So I just wanted to tap in and wish everybody a Ramadan Mubarak.
Also, I believe today is the beginning of Lent, or yesterday was.
Happy morning, raw.
Get your titties out, get your beads.
It's also fire horse season.
So we moved into a whole other space of energy, and I feel myself also moving into another space of energy.
And for this Ramadan, I have decided that I am going to fast visual media of TV, movies, and social media.
So Views for a Mandalan will be during the month of Ramadan, and that is going to cause you to look it up.
During the month of Ramadan, Views for a Mandalan will be taking place at 6 p.m. Eastern on Wednesday nights.
So I look forward to seeing you all there, getting your iftar of information and community.
And lean into this very auspicious time of energy convergence.
Ask yourself the tough questions, and, you know, allow yourself to be open to receiving.
I just put out a new moon musing, so go to my substack or just check the link that I am putting below in the caption.
And, you know, get another taste of what I hope is insight that inspires.
It's so funky.